[
{
  "question": "while(x > 0){\n    x--;\n}",
  "answer": "while x > 0:\n    x -= 1",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while x > 0:\n    x--",
    "while x > 0\n    x = x - 1",
    "while x > 0\n    x--"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(i <= 10){\n    System.out.println(i);\n    i++;\n}",
  "answer": "i = 0\nwhile i <= 10:\n    print(i)\n    i += 1",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "i = 0\nwhile i < 10:\n    print(i)\n    i++",
    "i = 0\nwhile i <= 10:\n    print(i)\n    i--",
    "i = 0\nwhile i < 10:\n    print(i)\n    i--"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(true){\n    // code here \n}",
  "answer": "while True:\n    # code here",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while true:\n    # code here",
    "while(1):\n    # code here",
    "while True\n    # code here"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(count != 0){\n    count--;\n}",
  "answer": "while count != 0:\n    count -= 1",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while count:\n    count -= 1",
    "while(count != 0)\n    count -= 1",
    "while count > 0:\n    count--"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(num < 10 && flag){\n    num++;\n}",
  "answer": "while num < 10 and flag:\n    num += 1",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while num < 10 || flag:\n    num += 1",
    "while(num < 10 && flag):\n    num++",
    "while num < 10 and flag\n    num += 1"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(i >= 0){\n    i--;\n}",
  "answer": "while i >= 0:\n    i -= 1",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while(i > 0):\n    i--",
    "while i != 0:\n    i -= 1",
    "while i > 0:\n    i -= 1"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(x != 0 && y != 0){\n    x--;\n    y -= 2;\n}",
  "answer": "while x != 0 and y != 0:\n    x -= 1\n    y -= 2",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while x != 0 || y != 0:\n    x -= 1\n    y -= 2",
    "while(x != 0) and (y != 0):\n    x--\n    y -= 2",
    "while x != 0 and y != 0\n    x -= 1\n    y -= 2"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(count > 0){\n    count--;\n    System.out.println(count);\n}",
  "answer": "while count > 0:\n    count -= 1\n    print(count)",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while count:\n    count = count - 1\n    print(count)",
    "while(count > 0)\n    count--\n    print(count)",
    "while count > 0:\n    count == 1\n    print(count)"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(flag == true){\n    // code here \n}",
  "answer": "while flag == True:\n    # code here",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while flag:\n    # code here",
    "while(flag):\n    # code here",
    "while flag = True:\n    # code here"
  ]
},
{
  "question": "while(count >= 10){\n    // code here \n}",
  "answer": "while count >= 10:\n    # code here",
  "wrongAnswers": [
    "while count > 10:\n    # code here",
    "while(count >= 10):\n    # code here",
    "while count => 10:\n    # code here"
  ]
}
]